<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Patrick Gatewood&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.patrickgatewood.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Patrick Gatewood&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.patrickgatewood.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>👋 Hello, Hugo!</title>
      <link>https://blog.patrickgatewood.com/blog/posts/hello-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.patrickgatewood.com/blog/posts/hello-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Welcome! You&amp;rsquo;ve found my first blog post. Hugo is an awesome open-source static site generator with a super active community.
I&amp;rsquo;ve chosen Hugo as my blog framework so I can learn more about static site generators and post some write-ups of what I&amp;rsquo;m up to without needing to manually create my site or worry about a CMS. As with most blogs, I expect everything on this site to be content-driven, so Hugo is a great fit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Adapt Existing Apps for SwiftUI</title>
      <link>https://blog.patrickgatewood.com/blog/posts/how-to-adapt-existing-apps-for-swiftui/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 17:54:17 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.patrickgatewood.com/blog/posts/how-to-adapt-existing-apps-for-swiftui/</guid>
      <description>Now that iOS 14 has been released to the public, SwiftUI and Combine are looking more and more attractive as you choose how to build your next greenfield app. But what about your existing applications? If you’re ready to drop iOS 12 and blaze new trails with SwiftUI, congratulations–and prepare yourself for an exciting journey.
So you’ve shipped your app’s iOS 13 updates, added dark mode, and dropped iOS 12 support… now what?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Have a Successful Internship</title>
      <link>https://blog.patrickgatewood.com/blog/posts/how-to-have-a-successful-internship/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 17:54:17 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.patrickgatewood.com/blog/posts/how-to-have-a-successful-internship/</guid>
      <description>Whether you’ve just landed an exciting internship for next year or you’re right in the middle of an internship at your dream agency, it’s up to you to get the most out of your experience. You decide what you take away from it, so check out these guidelines on how to design your internship to help you grow as an individual, your way.
Full article: https://willowtreeapps.com/ideas/how-to-have-a-successful-internship</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>